Coming
Ok
You have a stranger of the minute I heard this is a rocking you can grow up
Get access to the cork
Service 2 minutes
I have exposed then you have to get
No
What are the Euro
I think maybe
Looks legit
I believe this is one of them
Can you do this one again
Negotiate
Hello this is for you this is a fancy corkscrew not going in
I'm screwing the screw in the top is already now like
There is a particular way I know
Coming out
And then we bought it you know
I got
First thing I want to do is that you want to peel away
Always cut below this
We want to place the top
Single yellow bottle
Little Lever
Cancel
This is my favourite auto opening wine
You twisted down I think it is easier to apply pressure on the corkscrew
Is Ireland supposed to come out
Down
I was told
That if you can hear the bells
Correctly in the fire
Put the barber to my list
Security and
Open a bottle of wine
Contact with the Wind that's going to change the flavour profile I make sure I'm nice and
So there's no chance to the foil
Is going to come into contact with
Listen to do is drive the screw into the you can do it an angle so we can find the setup and just
Is designed to sit on the lip of the wine bottle support that the dark side of this lever
Is it against your hand
Gently Paul
Rene simply for here
Don't worry about the break in the glass
The point
Turn back in