Call
Shirley
Whipped cream never made with cream before
I've only had whipped cream
It's going to be like in Keswick today
I said this before I came in
Is it going to be poor in a few
Units of cream
Oh no
Oh this is in a bowl
I think you put this in here powdered stuff
Baby baking soda
I'm sure there's an appropriate amount I don't know what that is
I'm not a lady from the Victorian use a helmet
Ok this is happening
Bubbling
Twerking
Ananda Shake
Until we have whipped cream
How long will it take
Freezer
Suggesting
I'm going to make with cream and homemade whipped cream with cream I need a bowl
Starting with a bore straight from the freezer because the corner of things are
Heavy cream
You get pasteurized milk it will be easier and faster
For the heavy cream in
I made you a little powdered sugar
That is going to break up a little easier than my granulated I prefer granulated because
Has cornstarch in it and it tastes so good
I would normally do it this way for a person that ever it's basically just a back and forth as a
I'm sweating if I do this everyday I would never have to do any sort of our next
This is new gold
You are a star on love so there doesn't get all over you
Will it start to look like this we getting close
Can I see the ripples from the beaters because
50 weeks on my cycle meringue you might make butter
Success
That sound
That's my queen
Whipped cream
That's great
Put my face in the snow
Navigate to Lakeside
What I'm going to do this at my worst have a nice cold beer
It's a nice cold heavy cream
And then we're going to add some sugar and this is key
Is two different types of sugar people tend to put in whipped cream
What I like to use this plane granulated sugar ok
Is confectioners sugar and generally Pokémon starting this and I feel like it makes my work play mode on
Something I just enough sugar to get a sweet up the cream
And the reason that I earned it now it's because if we had it later my work is going to be great
Navigate to our waste and start whipping in this week's
And when we wish for you there a risk so you can see when I was staring was making a bubble go right now and wish
It's making a ton of bubbles give yourself a little stability by holding onto the ball
Getting sick now we want to whip this to soft Peaks right I don't want to go too far with it
Is it going to forward
Eventually alternative sweet butter nice and fluffy
Is forms can a really soft velvety piece on the top of my wish
Ok I'm done