Naked by these at the store already
Cooked
Ok what is
Pink nails
Can I fill an Avengers film
The outside
Trying to think of what method One cause me a chat my fingers off
I'm going to do with my hands
Why are there so many left
Doesn't seem to be cooperating with me to well
That was a nice
How do I export an area
Now time to intervene this bad boy
How do you get rid of these engines
I'm going to cut it open
I see the van
Minerals
Feels like glass that is so weird
Yeah I've no idea what I'm doing
Reveille the shrimp poop well you know them
I don't know how to do it
Ok I can do this
Slip along the back
Can you pull the tail off
Turn the lights to Teal just pull for just have a pension
So now what
This is the day it's blue it looks like our veins that's would you want to eat some people
Call Graham
Big favour
Put down through the back
Oh look it's coming out
Who are is
Is
I'm kosher so
I'm going to say no
Sorry
Compare two methods with the more traditional why you want to start by grabbing here
And then working away
Around the strip
From the feet on one side
Sophie on the other and just feeling that back we can leave the Tail on
For something like this room packed in or we can simply just sort of picture of the tail
Mpl back
And remove the telephone this year
Paring knife
Come through the paradise directly on the backside of the shrimp and asking to review up the van here which you can see
This is the digestive tract of the shrimp and then
Just like that for the second letter of your stream sideways on your work surface
Come in with the blade facing away from you
And you're going to both peel back
And slice
At the same time
So appealing their shell
Error opening up the digestive tract
I'm just pulled a vein
Searching for sweetness
Can you divert
Meaning of shrimp
I'm done
Tell me DVLA