Roman Towers mum do if she says this is just going to hate me forever
Jason Adam Baker
Let's stick with brownies more than advertised
My grandmother was a real Baker Street from scratch apple pies peach cobbler
Cinderella
Wa
Apple pear slices
I'm sure there is a tool that would be good
This looks like
Lidl duvet
Screw you Apple
It's like in apple pie
Make a pasty
I don't know what to do with this
Alright so step one you again if you've got an apple you've got a twisted and say that ABC
Whether you lend is the person that you're going to end up with for the rest of your life
That was
This Apple
Colouring half
Can see some nice spices
Tried to take out the seeds
My father make apple pie
It's the best slice Mesa diesel real singer
Is elaborate ways to slice an apple if we're getting it for a pie we don't want to remove the skin so that's going to be the first thing that I'm going to do
What's my Apple skinless the easiest Wi-Fi to remove the core is to cut the Apple into
4 pieces which is the same
Just at the side of the cord here
I have just to the side of the corgi
Play my Apple down and then
Two more wedges
Cork gone for making up I am probably going to slice all of these approximately 1/2 in
6 something like that
And something here just come out through
And then I have nice even slices and natural important in life
That's pretty much what I would do you know just put it inside little piping
Apple pie