Go time
You have to make puncture first have a weak spot maybe this
Trewetha something
Baby news this with the Habit myself if I try
A Mexican a whack it with a clever I feel like that's something I've seen before
Oh boy that is not making nearly as much as I thought it would
There has to be a better way than this
Ok so
Is There Something I know
Two holes
Air pressure
When I get the water out of your first
Ok
I'm going to describe Muhammad how to make a piercing
Here we go
Can you crack a coconut
Screwdrivers
Will use it for food later she never going on people
The reason
Immersion
Tricks and it might require a little bit of safety precautions so the first thing to do is coconut water
Basically going to hold a screwdriver on the eyes with her on the end
Two of them
I just drain the coconut water
Because we don't want to lose all that good coconut water
Add the coconut water is going to end up
Google shake sound
Now
Here is the fun part
We're going to take the Hammer
Play crack the sky open now going to be most prominent and you can see if you work at the end of the
Come to the centre of the coconut
Rocket Ride on that
Ivory Ella
Find the next prominent ridge on a coconut
Continue
Three of them so I'm going to find the third
And we should be able to link all 3 together with this last
And that's how we open the cooker
Coconut
You know what you do with this