That line from
A list of artichoke as in heart
New dawn
This is my first time holding an artichoke in my entire life
Heart in the middle
Hotel
There's nothing left
Where is it what is the thing that we eat
I just want to peel it off
Opening a present inspection something inside but
What is there's nothing in
Flower
Christy
I think I know where the heart is but
Yes
I do like since it only has
Will using a heart to heart with different animals
I'm going to stop this
Is
Tell me what I just sliced Turkey down the centre of
It's not happening
First thing's first
An appeal after few of the leaves camera pattern
It's musical
Listen to it
Play clean
The stem
I'm going to cut off the top
White down
Taking out the trash
Nifty
Texture
And then
Dip in the water
The lemon keeps them from getting Brown that my channel
It doesn't look right to me but the heart isn't there
Better way to do this
Ok we're going to find the heart of the art
The first thing I want to do is just removed the really loose leaves on the outside of the artichoke
Is just looking to expose the
Lighter yellowish green colour
Put on the inside stem of the artichoke is completely edible as well I'm just going to be off the top five
Woolley Park that's the outside texture
Leave the inside Park which is tender
Towards the
Just as leaves off
And work my way around
The next find the top of the lowermost
We're gonna cut it from straight down the green leaves on the outside are the party we want to get rid of
The leaves turn yellow you've made it to the heart
Depending on the preparation method for the audit
You may want to remove the choke just take the spoon
Dentist
That's the joke right there with artichokes
Sensitive meaning that they turn brown quickly
So when you have your other job
Exposing clean then you want to quickly get that submerged into water
Water with a little bit of lemon juice will really help because the acidity will help stop the oxidation process which
I think I broke her