Because I said so
I've never made a villain
I don't know
Portions
Ok
Virgin olive oil
Primary fuels like you put the master there
I know it's a setup look like
I'm going to beat up
Mustard or whatever sinking to the bottom of the Milky Way
Terrible
I have no idea
How to make a vinegar
OK Google is a 6 to 1 ratio 6 oil 1 vinegar
I prefer 2 to 1
Start Waze
One spoon of Mr
Take some vinegar
Do some extra virgin olive oil
Try to mix the vinegar and B12 together
Slowly
Dressing doesn't separate
Amazon
Everybody taste
If you love you
Go home
Ok so we're going to do is make a x a great here to start with a good amount of oil now I'm not really
Specifically measuring this year but when you're aiming for it
About a 3 to 1 ratio
Oil to vinegar
Measuring cup
And my vinegar is going to record into the bowl
Dijon mustard here and mustard seeds are really good
Emulsifier that means that they're really good at holding two things that don't want to go together
Together
Not the first thing I'm looking forward my babe is it is really well blended in the Formula so sort of going
A visual indicator to make oil into the mixture
And I want to be with me constantly as I had
If you noticed that you're mixing balls moving around a little bit while whisking just take a kitchen towel
Slightly damp that's helpful too
Big lorry
I can put my mixing boring here and another word for getting away from me while I'm so whiskey
Oil into the boss
In the key here is to go slow the entire time
That's it
Taste
Call boy
If you were looking for a dressing that has exclusively the taste of mustard was also feeling intensely
Can I recommend
Where's vinegar I just made