Million viewers are going to Hinder this and say
Second-hand diving shark news
It's been a long time
I want to go home with all my
This looks like a job for me
Give me some
Particularly
I think so
Oyster is now
Akash open
And then if I had crazy glue
I could put it this shell back together
Is no problem
I think is good
Favourite things in the entire world
Nothing really sorry just want to do
Women
Just on my way around and tell her
Massage to get juicy there I need his leg
In one Swift move
Circle wall around it
From the shelf
Oyster here you can always identify an oyster is having a blue top and a bottom
Changeable upside is going to be the bottom shelf in the flat inside is going to be the Top Shop
To come in at the points and we're going to find the hinge is probably a good idea to wear a bra
Non dominant hand
The Quays opening Easter is about twisting not pushed into the head
Go back and forth until you feel the open up there
Manhole disguise
I'm going to try the note
The inside of the top shelf slide in between
And slide ride across that does this separate the muscle of the Oyster
From the shell on a
Ok so that my
Easter is
Nicely preserved on the inside