Ok so high
Ok
Snake
I'm gonna try I think I can figure it out
Call Kay
Maybe this won't work with it
What's the weather
This is cute
Oh my god
This is terrifying
Turn off
Anymore for the sake of my hand like a hexagon
Structural integrity of the pineapple is a falling apart
Ok we're going to cut this pineapple
First
Off
The top
Turn off the bar
Cut down the sides to take the skin off
Probably nobody
Go down the middle and get rid of a corn
Take this down in the cinema
And now I'm coming into the
Covering up ok
To do when you're getting a pineapple top in the bottom of the pineapple
So that things are Rolling away from us when we try and catch
Pineapple we want to stand up and work your way down the sides
Is to get rid of the eyes which are the dad's right here
Without losing too much flesh ok so you want to get in
About a half an inch in word
Working away
That was pretty good
I'm happy with that I'm outside and I'm going to start putting this into
Desks
On this afternoon to do is take the Rings by hand
Rotating
My way around the corner
The goal here is just to get that
Core of the sun
If you're using a pineapple coring tool
Which is
This guy right here
You can really just go straight into the top twist the tour
Take the core out this way this is a fine method but I find that you'll get a substantial amount of waste this way
The core
What's the weather in the centre of the pineapple regardless of the size of your penis
You end up losing the sort of outside edge of the pipe
It certainly works and we're going to get Rings out of it
I did it
The ring
Right right
Wow
A delicious piece of pineapple