I'm star
Because I have never
My kitchen
Ever
Cause I hardly have any food my kitchen anyway
I'm going to explain to you what these different vegetables and fruits are
What I do
These are
OK Google look like
Alien body parts
What are the news look like
I don't know what these are
Larvae like really
Worm looking tuba
Pictures of ginger
Maybe a baby yam or potato
This might just be a carer
Oh that's very is it a squash
It's almost like ginger or like a carrot but it's not
Also looks like the babies in Harry Potter
I know
This is turmeric in a fresh form
How much are used to seeing as a pallet space is so
Good for you
I have a lot of health properties information
Turmeric
People never see that too
In it's raw form
Now there's a simple face mask teeth whitening
Cappuccino 3200 cappuccino
What different flavour is in the stuff that you get powder
Little sharper the more vibrant and basically just be the chapter separate and using in soups
If anything you want actually colour yellow
These guys
Crazy claw
What is this
Is it a secret room
I've never seen this before my life begins
Like a weird coconut sort of thing is this mangosteen this might be jackfruit
Maybe is a passion fruit
Boyfriend
Is Italy cheap
This might be a leech
Maybe the Hairy lychee
This is a rambutan
Rambutan
I think it's
Orangutan is Ashley Close 11
You just can't break into it I need it like a stone in the middle
You just basically the Sweet food
What is
No idea
What that
Seems dangerous
It's a candle
Squash cousin two finger line
Looks like a prehistoric cucumber
John
Diamond
Private boards
Zucchini that has been crossed with a brain
Something now
This is some sort of melon
A bitter melon
Crack open
Yes it's better
Is there vitamin C in American cooking
The texture of maybe a boiled potato at the end and has Cannabis slowly bit of flavour
This is Park
It's some kind of Rule
The taro root ginger
Passata
Jicama
But I don't think that's what it is
A.m.
Ugly ginger
This is a femur
Caveman's Mallet
So familiar
Is horseradish
I think this is horseradish
Horse riders people use every day especially for the Jewish
Horse racing titles
In the storm it's much more pungent than you were getting a job
You just
Will salt and vinegar delicious a little more sharper a little more bite
Then the stuff you actually getting the chair
Hello
Samsung
There Siri
Mung beans
Great great grandfather be
Beans
Alien hair
What is wrath
The end is a Hurley
I don't
Long name
Ambience Sydenham
Cheltenham upstairs by them
Along these are another interesting thing
Can you retrieve these pretty much any way you would treat a green bean
Are diesel really good stir-fry
Delicious
What the heck is this
Oh my god
Ok this is something terrifying
Shockingly
How
This hurts
The stem is mushy and is it some sort of
This is a pine cone
This is a jackfruit
Dragon
I can't remember
Begins with
Adrian
Smyths Derry
Has very strong
Roma
Like cat pee and vanilla it's not allowed in Airport
Ronaldo the travel with
Because of the smell
The internet was not lying
Is this the most disrespectful fruit in the world
Koreans are very notorious for their smell in
And in our faces airport buses public places in Asia not even allowed to bring it
Where to see fresh in the United States and Southeast Asia
People are a really crazy battery no really because of the smell
Can I have the savoury flavour to it
Directly really
What are you
This is the end of a strange alien passion fruit
But I don't think it is at
No shower before tenants
Dragon fruit
Winton South American cup of tyre
Black and white speckles
Taste like a sponge
Think
Unless but at least we have a dragon through it's a really nice interior it's white with little black specks
Sweet
Has like a little bit like an apple or peach like flavour basically in salads
Turn off with other fruit
I hope this helps
Naturally letting you know how to use them
What is the score between Luton
I do not know any of these
I don't get any
I got one right
3 red
Which one cylinder
I got four eyes
I got a mole
100%