In home now
I'm not going
Everyone has
Lol opening
I have no idea
Goggles goggles
Safety first
You do not need this
No
Well I think so well
Core
Kinda like a Cyprus in the kid that said in the back of the class is actually pretty fun
Probably did a little too
It was not as crumble
Contact when they are there
I hit him too hard that one night
If you like these are one
Beautiful honest
This one at 4
This is a
Pictures of bad boy in there you have to put it in the summer and put it in a long
Wine
Oh yeah
We're going to hold it so that it doesn't
Go into your eyes
Not done Force too hard
Otherwise you'll break the entire
Not in the middle of it will seem right down the middle hair
I would think
You get the screwdriver in the same and give it a whack
Do you want me to do with the way my mother used to do it
Inside this
To try putting it up so your history on Steam
A crack a walnut here
This is not a difficult task but you do need to make sure that you get the right in to start with
No problem it will open that way but that's a little bit messy around your kitchen
So my favourite method inside and outside they're all this
This is where you don't want to be
Put the sky over
So that you can see your flat inside on the bottom of a walnut
And there usually is a little bit of a crack right in there and this is your point of entry into your wallet if
When somebody is banging with a hammer
You can use anything
Cut your hair
Going gently
Twist
It should be cleanly and
I've never done this before but just on the edge of a spatula
Safe to use
They should be all that we need
I'm going to find that openings
Going to stick the corner of the spatula in there
If you don't
Who was the actual top of the Nutcracker
And this guy is actually designed to do this
Simple enough to just putting a knife in between the Nutcracker
And tracking it
It comes apart amazing how well