Play goes nothing
Oh my gosh French style omelette
Ok this butter
I'm going to have to break up the eggs how many do you think we need
You know what I'm saying is all of them
When will shell in there
So far so now I'm going to beat the eggs
I think I've ever even use the worst before
So now we have a herbal blend
Herbs
Sprinkle
Scattered
This is
Ok if you have high cholesterol this is not be omelette for you
Something's Happening
French omelette is almost done
It's already looking unattractive
Weather for
Ok scrambled eggs ok
I think this looks perfect
Looks ok
This is something that would scare most children
I don't know what the French say it is
So
Stop 1px
2 x
You don't need to put the butter in
Why not
And then you whip in your amulet
I'm just waiting for it to set a little bit
I'm really gone for cheese I'm going to skip it on only half of it
Inside of a
The fun park
Flip it over once I'm flipping this site over
Flip it
Perfect
Ok
I'll be happy to eat this
Meaning of everybody
Today we're going to make a two-egg omelette so what are you looking for here is a few really distinctive
Is there a difference in American salon
The first looking for is no colour on the ex as opposed to the Browning that you might see on a traditional sort of American style
The inside of the army should be slightly custody
But not quite ready we're going over easier
The last thing that were looking for is 3
We have all the armour over itself as opposed to just holding it in half
In order to get that for me custody text you in the inside we need to really make sure that
Eggs are completely even and smooth in terms of the mixture
Police station
Tbsp butter for an omelette
The Exeter go on the piano as soon as the butter is melted in foaming
The first thing I'm gonna do is just gently Scramble disabled
Will we need the top of the eye to be a little bit
Before we start to leave it
Start to form a sort of skin on the bottom side of the pain relief from the pain and
Just stuck it off
Now
You can see the egg in the centre of the Penistone little bit liquid
Moving around the Keeper from burning until we see the egg that in the centre of the armour just started gel
To be honest
But not
A little bit of goat cheese
Right on the middle of the army
Flight dispatcher London
Every day fold in on itself
The next thing you're going to do here is for the army in the other way and then roll towards the back
The pier
Ok
Just like this
And they were simply going to
Tilt the pan and slide the omelette out on its own
The motion is sort of a rotating away from your
Salerno's
Yeah just give me like 10 minutes then I can finish this and then
Cameras