Ok not sure what I'm supposed to do with this
No idea
Where are first got to take a look at it oh my god
Oh dear
Does anyone buy an idiot
I've got the head off
Are you this
Oh god that's not working I think I need a shorter nice with a girl
Oh my god I broke you guys coming bored I'm so sorry
I need to get the bones out somehow
Just tried to cut into the bottom of a fish and nothing more
This fish is resilient to be like starting out
I've no idea what I'm doing right now
I would really love to know how to do this is supposed to be messing I'm currently
Ok I'm hopefully this before but see how we do
First I cut off the head of fish
Ok cut the tail
Official
Take your fillet knife
With the bone
On one side of the spine
I think we feel lazy
There's all kinds of good coming out
Body feels weird
Around this year there's a couple different ways to do this the first way here we're just going to come right behind it
We're going to make one
Straight down
Until we get the spine
Make a small car out of the tail
I'm just going to connect the dots from this car
To the sky
Using the phone on the top as a guy
For when I'm working I'm just using the tip of the blade
Just open the Sky app to allow me to see where does the time work
Ok
Now we have two apps
What we can do is work our way down from the top of the fish
Where we can do the other afternoon where we started from
Tell me another night sideways making sure that we use their guide
To determine where and left
And then in this particular matter
What we're going to do is just simply crack straight through the bar
Deserve the fishes river
The general
Fairly delicats
Really easier track right through those guys
You're going to end up with all of your ribs right here in the
What we need to do is then remove the Rib section of the fillet
Take my life and I'm just going to come down at an angle
I want my knife resting against the ribs
Here's the Rib section here with the belly what's remove that
This is my complete
On the second day what we're going to do is the other method for how to remove the fish to make a diagonal coming from the top of the
Any just making sure that you went behind the practice
And again here
Make my cat
Just like the other method I'm going to connect the dots from where I made my first
To where I make my
I'm not going deep this is my guide
For making my
The first mess
Going to do here is go ahead and come down from the top of the fish and we're going to make more sweeping
Gentle cats
And if you can hear that
I want to hear the
Light
Clicking against the rear
That's a good indicator that I'm right on the spine and shoulders any flesh
Westbury
In the flying
So as I'm working in a bar
But I can do is go ahead and come all the way through working towards the front of the fish
What I want to do is just open the Sky app and lifting
Leaving all the bones behind
We have a second floor
Which matches the first one
Is Donald the second method moving all the ribs
For attach
Little football