Sniff it first
The Spice Girls
Usually the craziest place that I'll go for it it's like
Oregano
It smells so familiar
Arcus Redditch
6 percenter based on colour alone at this is Sage
Search
No that's a
Common
Gas smells like almonds
Everything is kind of smells like
Really nice tea party flavour and the best way to open up the flavour in the dish
2 this is a bit of oil or butter beginning of the cooking process
I went to Cardiff
This is very tasty
Spice
I think it's too much
Turmeric
Really healthy Spice that's really really good for you and it's a really nice subtle flavour that
Permeates the dash on a sort of person
Spicy
This is something red
Look at the colon cinnamon
Cayenne pepper
That's coming in
Can we have hot paprika as we have sweet paprika and smoked paprika is it a really different flavour profile
The table comes from a dried sweet pepper and a hot pepper comes from
Ginger powder
Powdered onion onion powder
That's
Arania I'm hoping this is
Garlic that is garlic
I like to put that on my pizza This Is Us
Really really strong it's on how to overpower and finishing your dish with dried garlic and other really released
Flava Flav
How's things
Dark brown
Space
Saffron
Classic steak seasoning
This is 100% mixture of spices actually comes from different types of chili
Are combined together and we have a range of Hotness that's available and this really great space
Base of Flavour in stews and soups and sauces
I don't know what that is
This one is
Nervous system
Forget the name
I don't know what this is
This is curry whatever stains my hair
Is going to be the curry
This one is Kerry
You're basic free blend from tons of different spices
Next together in everybody's recipe is different so there's no standard procedure with Harry Potter relationship around
Just like a lot of other devices in really benefit from long slow cooking in from being added at the beginning of a cooking class
In here
We have chilli powder
Yeah this one stumped me I really can't forget