ðŸ†
Music
I have an emoji
This is the enemy from Curtis Carroll Dallas
Hubert
Cuban dance
It's getting the skin off so there is a good start
Square at the end
Hillingdon half term
So much eggplant here to enjoy anyway
I think I messed this up
The least efficient way to do this
We'll see what this does
Diasorin
Back
What's that a Cuba
Yeah I cut myself
Eggplant
Skip the bottom
I prefer this skin to be on
Credit to me some
Thanks
Play into slices first about
Just under an inch deck
We really not mind the seed
So they're just
Out of matchsticks
Mcube
Dyson
Should I feel it or not most of the bitterness in the iPlayer comes from the seeds in the skin
Ok so if you're worried about it being bitter
Go ahead and take the skin off one really funny that you can do
Strips
Flavour from the Peel
Without being overwhelming
Stems that have to cut through it and cut in half
Mayflies all the way down if I want to do a half moon shaped baby for roasted eggplant
I'm just like this if I ever I want a dice my plant or something like that
Play like that and then I'm just going to see you make a horizontal cut across the front line
Turn the Sky the other direction on the board to make two or three cats
Maghrib Bath
Into my ankle
I'm going to take my life
Hair licence
Fingertips Tab 10 I'm just going to come down
And
Easy
And then we have an hour
That's a big handful cubes baby
This is my finger from getting app