It's that time of season
Alright
I hate this
What is it I will call to Bell pepper my girlfriend gifts from Australia
Capsicums
That's fine
Go for it
I have never
What are the
Perfect
Can I sing
The smell in hoover
So what do I do after a D&C
I don't want to be
Someone taught me how to do this
You and I
Remember
So what you do this take this out
Like a pumpkin cut in half
Alexa and Karen ages
And then there's inside Park you can do
Call
What all do is I cut out the kiss
Dangerous jet Lee
I know there's like a fancy way to do it
This app
Play most recent
How many kg are left hand
Turn off light
Slices app
We are sliced
The work of art
So just like any other vegetable find yourself or flat sides for your vegetables not rolling around when you cry
Miniature in the bottom your
Basically you have natural seem so you can see this sort of has a square shape and I'm gonna follow those natural scenes
As my divided
Work my way down the pepper
King of the court
Inside the pepper you'll have some white this is the path we want to remove it going to come in with my parents
And
Turn that radio
Just like that making a horizontal
Once I have that removed
Then I'm single
Come through you'll find it much easier to slice of pepper with the skin side down
If I put the skin up
The night has a tendency to countdown soften the skin because of the flash underneath is much softer than that
Skin side down
Heard