That's
Little bit
I'm using because I am not
Probably my favourite
Slightly
For the heart
Put butter on both sides of butter
You put it on the bread
This is going to be really gross
Play Jesus
Individually
News
It'll be great
You can have some
That is 6 and 6 slices of cheese
Go on
And it's summer again
Turn up to
As hi is it
Ok something is definitely burning now
The more flipping you do the better because it is
It's a bit crispy brie
I think it's ok
I personally like my
I did not cook this evening we are all you see are you still see slices that's the incorrect way to do it
I'm going to
Underneath
Does this is what's going to save you from burning
Do you want to butter both sides
There's no point in trying to make a grilled cheese without
So we have a variety of
Archies
Monster
The butter in the pan I have to be careful cuz you better can burn
The other side
Too much
Siri
Sunny House
Very good
The big question is the UK
I like the cut
On the diagonal
I'm a stranger
Just logo butter
On the pan
Is it raining at night
Smokey rideaway
I think is the key for the really classicroses
Is that butter has
Ingredients that are not just your fat
In the pan
Put the mixture experiment
I'm going to go with a slice of Cheddar
And also
Because it's really really good soft melting cheese
Let it go
To keep an eye on the butter what were looking for is no smoke I'm looking for the foaming and listening for the
I'm just doing a bit of a shake to make sure that nothing stuck to the pan
So what we gonna do is go ahead
This
Remind me to melt before the bread buns
We are ready to go
Can we have it that's are you saying she's in there
Play some LT with Cheddar and monster in there too