Before
Cabbage
This is a cabbage
It's called something
I'm so sorry
I don't understand the point of ice and snow
Skip the singer always wash your vegetables
Because it looks not right
Go for it
I am reading the West
Turn off the lights
Roll It All app
I know this doesn't look great right now
We have
Let us a whole head of iceberg
Tasteless
You can probably get the 99 Cent store and you would pay like for 99 in a bag
30 seconds of handsome and thinking about your ex
Salad
Can you use
I take off
Like the top players in it's the best
Is there amazing
Straight down the middle
This is
No one wants to eat salad
With big pieces letters
Is loaded up with bacon bits
Blue cheese dressing this is one way to do it
Not too big not too small
Play Steven mother truck
Pause
Where do you chop some lettuce SO31 ahead of iceberg
Things that roll around the heart and the very first thing I want to do when I'm having lettuce onion tomato or any
Is the earth flat
Score of the weather's of and put that facing the ceiling in my very first the entire point is the
Something Blue
Iceberg or any other heading that if you have a look on that actually going to work
Everything together
I'm just going to
Turn it into 2 Quarter
That's it
I have the option then I could maybe slice really thin slices of lettuce like
Put it on top of something like that
What I want to do is then go ahead and one more time
In your nearest then I'm going right through the core
That's going to keep it from falling apart
Travelling tonight
Bitesize pizza
Can I have my wireless chart
Before I turn this into a nice salad
I need to wash it
Before the chocolate but how you gonna get in between the waves that why so it is just like this
Transferred to a salad spinner and dryer
There is our lettuce for salad
Lettuce
Add server printer in the shaft
Reselling
Call Aberdeen