This is and it's making me so uncomfortable
Do I have to pick it up
Go on Siri
Ok this is not a vegan show
Touch these things this is the story
This I believe is
I got this
Like a piece of lemon
Stuff for Korean BBQ
Short rib
Beef short rib
Get some Syrian is bad boys in prison
Even need the middle of the road
This is a beef short rib
Ok comes from the centre section of the room can I come in around the bottom side of the cow this is a really great day
Low and slow
Moisty not good for throwing on the grill
No
This is the other
Honestly clean products
I don't like this game anymore looks like a purse
Martin Thornton
It looks like a swim cap
Remind me
Who wants to be seen but not
Papery
Outlook
If my life depended on it I couldn't really tell you
Placenta
What's it called
Stomach
Remember the name
No thank you
Tripe is the lining of one of the
Well it looks very tasty
It doesn't taste like
This is true
This is from the digestive system of the cow is really really
Has certainly flavoured on its own and this really benefits from long low and slow cooker
To bring out the flavour
When you look
This is this is what you looking for
The word is coming to me
Don't Snapchat
It's the defining part of a bowl
Which is
This is fascinating
I would expect to see like
Tune in here somewhere
Muscular
I'm not sure what this is but I probably playlist
Looks like steak and I think state comes from the
Looks attractive
The hair stick
Which is part of the animals whole like breathing
Muscle centre like skirt steak
The Hanger steak that's a right here this one has a really
Easy way to identify and that's the there's a member in that runs down the centre and everything a stick
The green that runs in a v pattern so you can see the grain here these lines
Going here and coming from the other side that's how you can recognise the Hangouts
Known as
Play or butchers steak this is the only sticking on the calendar is only one it's in the centre of the cow is supposed to have
Ring on the left
Oh my god
No idea what this is
Order of songs for
Give me the weather
Are all these parts available
Drinking
Kidneys
Net
It is so hard
Beefheart
I definitely see some like
Ventricles
I believe they're called I don't know
Holsworthy
Do you want to come out and you can see the Chambers
The heart
This is a portion of a beef for this gives you an idea of how big a beef heart actually is and we only have
Corner of it right here so you can pick you up I'll bring the whole thing with you
Velasquez I know exactly what it is
Touch this thing
The Rings
That's a top
Tongue
How tall how tall is a huge cock
Not for me thank you I'm having used this is very good for you and if you shut up
Don't like tongue
So gross I can't
Price of the Galaxy in support of the
How do you cook
It looks like a steak on the underside
It has all the Little Lights
Three parts of Italian stuff
IPad
When your tasting the Carol you just have to think about the cows he seemed you
This is a Celtic this needs to be cooked in slow but when it is really really really
Delicious
Cows eat grass all day don't get a lot of use and when muscle mass get a lot of use
To be a laptop
The other thing to know about the time we need
Peel the skin off of the sky
And it is your appeal after it's cooked
These are some of the beef cuts
That's all
Please set the way