What's my favourite food
Before this is gold to me
I've done this before I just
Go home
I'm going to be dramatic and I'm trying to get this I don't even know
I'm bringing it
When I go with my 50%
Perfect like a surgeon
I want to just
Something in the middle of finding stuff
How do you get the
After pill
See if I can do anything with you
God that's what doesn't work
Going to be a Snow Day
It's alright that I'm going
Since the mango massacre
Somatotype
Write the sentence after the side
No just like stack it up
And just make
Is nice little strips
Put it in space
Ironmongers in West rips life-size bites
It feels delicious
There's an old saying in Brazil that when you know how to cut a mango
You're ready to marry also I'll show you a little trick with mango
Recorded doing a porcupine
Is my grandmother a sister do
I want to bring a back
Mango like this
New comedies
What I'm looking at the mango there are going to be somewhere I Belong right so that's gonna be the indicator before using current
Directions to Pitt is going I want to face it's so the Narrow side is facing me this way
And that way I can come down the side without hurting a bit because the pit comes fairly wide
Actions if you want a nice taste nice and gently score and then we can actually turn it inside out
Like this and come across and remove all those huge pieces certainly we could do slicers as well
Using the same general technique
Just sliding
Horizontally along the skin
Tell me the sizes
So we have si stand
Next
Two different versions
Bon appetit
We're just
You have to try