This is
I mean
What hell is
So this is a plane
Shellfish
I love seafood
Would you like me to identify these creatures
Oh my god
The cyclical
Till
Giant mutated
Mastic
Ring Mum
This
To be to be alive
Stop
Is an Alaskan
This is the King Crab with King Crab legs
Super yummy
Stupid expensive
A part of a King Crab
And this is just one life so you can pick her up
The King Crab is a really good slightly sweet me there
Actually kind of work for will be like a Moreton Bay bug
Ok that actually give me
Does anyone know if this is disgusting
What's the weather
This is a pun
Believe this is a prawn
This is
Big time shrimp
Lobster
The lab
I think it's a lobster
This is a crawfish
Croydon
This has to be a
Alarm
Spanish 116
Nothing to live for
Photos of butter
Ok solicitor langoustine this is somewhere in between a shrimp and lobster and closely related
How old is next thing I was just
To weird Groves this is disgusting thing and everything
This is my idea
Looks like something out of Star Wars
An elephant trunk
Looks like elephant
Is this like a snail or octopus or something some sort of my claim
I know the Chinese
Harvest Samba
I actually do know this one is this one is a dirty Duck
Is it a good at on my favourite about
And they cut this partner and I make more points
Miami Springs weather
Country
Can a crazy looking
Really really big
This muscle that grows out of the claim is used to help the club Burrow into the into
She got a couple of
Meet
Inside
It's bubbling
We have your
Clamps
Dacia
Some people
Will clams with your grade in
Various sources and stuff
Is this a clown
Muscles
Muscle
What's this
How do you smell
I think
These are called cockles or clams
A video
Wipeout kids
A range of names that go in a Seat Altea
Confused by them
The reality is that the name Zack
The most types of
This shaped to correspond with the size
More than the typewriter
Little neck vs cherrystone vs atop
Are the same type of claim different sizes
I'm not sure what this is
I never seen this before my life is a proper job
Show which people eat this and find some way to get inside of
How can you put the cinema
This is not available to me
Brush my shoulders
Stampy
Another word for occupy
A porcupine
Think it might be a sea cucumber
Ceumannan and Eminem
CNN
This looks like a h
This is an urgent another song
This is your chance
Listen original
Sea urchin
At the beach
This guy radio this crazy looking thing is actually see and what we going to do when we eat this year
Inside of this thing of the spikes on the
Yes
Somehow both
Salah
How do I do it
Who knows
You just didn't
I don't even know if it's safe
This one is cute I like
Can I go hot dog
Like I say larvae in looks like a crab Lane but it's not a problem looks like
Can you spell that
Is there a clam it's not that scary looking I don't know the technical term for it
Razor
Very tasty
You can see why they might be called a razor clam that have the shape of a straight razor a barber with use
This is our variety of exotic
Ok idea
Can someone tell me when things are really can you tell me what is this
Cockles
And nothing to me
How to poop