You pull it takes a million years and then at the end you have a hard boiled egg so there's really no
Reward for Damien
Ok hard boiled egg
Looks too hard to do with your SIM using
The Pillar scratch the surface or
This might have to do with the peeling process I feel like shaking around
I'm just going to go right into it and use my
Going well
I'm taking up quite a bit of a
Oh no
Looking very pretty
Beauty and imperfection
Faster way to do it
Who must be a more efficient way to do this
Ok is to Jet Li
Crack the egg
I just roll it a little bit
I'm not sure what the magic is in the roll
Absolutely helps
And then I just kill
At the bottom is the air pocket and you want to get it from there
Getting around the edges
Almost there
That's my favourite a big piece comes on
Money shot
Here we go for the perfect hard-boiled egg
This is my hard boiled egg peeled
A healer
Islam ways to feel horrible
The key for me for peeling hard-boiled eggs
Naturally have a look so when you tap
On account
You'll see
On this site it broke but it still exist
Beer bubbles on this side and that's what I want to start
Because I want to try and get some water under the
Am I normally do as I tap it all the way around I don't just tap that one
Ice immersion in water
And then I start to appeal right to hear that membrane
Right I want to pull them away
I'm trying to start to get a little bit of water under
So I just keep on getting in the water
I'm pulling up
If the show comes away
Really easy
If you have little shards of fragments this also
Hey Google
Very dry