This is a mason jar filled with
Something green
Mum
Basil to eat it
Is a cilantro parsley
What does immense mean
I've never met
Anyway
Nicely
It's not that hungry today
It would make a nice centerpiece actually
Make me so proud right now
The weather
Pistol pistol
This is the modern that's a pastel that Castle is the more of this
The first
Actually made since I graduated College 2 months ago
Apart from Les arcs on the television
No no
Cafe until
Really
It's working
Play Spotify
That should do
Shut up
This is either
Cilantro or parsley in it
Poor taste
This is just
Some parsley
Curly parsley vs flat
Italian flag
Sleep
How to properly mince parsley
Tomorrow in Belfast
Of course I can look sexy boys
Out of how to start off with a lot you want to make sure that you really rinse it off
The best part about this is the leafy part of the ends first
Stems don't really taste good
My parsley first
So take the leaves off
Funfair
If you ever had
Onions
Juicing parsley
It gets rid of bad breath
Easiest way to mince parsley is too kind
Folder into itself
When s*** together
This is what you meant swear
Knitting memes
The smallest size
How to keep the point of Blade on the boarding
Get out
I'm really good in the kitchen
Parsley can be put in like a spaghetti sauce
Ready for a party party
Sprinkle on top of your lasagna
Poo poo poo poo poo
Anatomy
Italian flat leaf parsley and disconnects every kind of confusing Arabic
Shows similar to cilantro
I'm going to do in Midsomer this person right here is what
Just hold the Bunch by the stem and take my night at I'm going away for myself and I'm at my dad's swiping motion
From the start
Where can I get a few stems of going to sneak their way in there and I'll just go through and double check get everything bundle really
With my finger and thumb on the blade and then wrap around the grip
Rocking motion when I make these
I'm starting with the tip of the knife on the board
As I work I'm just sliding back and forth you'll see
Never leaves the surface of the cutting board
The amount of times that you go over the first
Completely depends on how final you want it
If I want to find a room in this one to do is collect my pile again in a minute
How many do the same thing and I come right back over it and just continue to mince
Bringing the species into smaller and smaller
That's all we know
Oh my god