You could use carrots for Hammersmith really
So much
You know
There was complete
Ok homes Perth
Can I cut the top off
My finger
TUI site
What are them by the carrot already
Sounds good
Like this
Arsenal
First take office starts on the end
Do you want to take the peel off
Is parties in thirds
You want them to be strong enough to let
Move the Hammers towards the face
I'm just running slightly diagnosed that you can x
Get more honest on you
Heading up in there
Just look at that
This is what he was hearing
So I'm going to peel this first
Does a relatively thin carrots so
I like to do what I'm doing with the vegetable this is
Carried into manageable size pieces based on the size so straight down
So through and I'm Gonna Cut that in half
And even
The perfect carrots