How to open a read correctly
Search party
That
What the heck is that
Please for Christmas last year but I never used it
This is not gonna end well
Where's my chicken tenderiser chicken this way powder seasonings can go with them
Chicken
These things seem like they're really important
Ray Grahams
Gnocchi
Eating on the floor
Who are the erg
Mountain of bread
I dabble in the breadcrumb no
I'm so afraid
Car park
Sticky
Make sure
Even recorded
Is dressed ready for the party
Put it in there
Just going to Krakow
What does turn it up to 4
Cardiff
Stream
Cook all the way
Can you hope and Pray for the best
I don't know how long is the best
30 seconds
Christmas outside right that bread
Turn on hallway
Be patient
Stay with me
Really cooking is a warm in a cold salmonella
Can you
I mean I don't know
I'm going in
Turn down
4 3 2 1
Britney Spears career at the hitmaker
Does chicken have died
Play the news
How do you make a slide
Now it's time to
It is completely wrong
Delicious
Immediate service to a child
Fried
Ok
I can do Friday
You have to code it you can just throw it naked into the
Pepper sauce
Termination errors
You can season the chicken or
You can see the flower of the chicken the better
Everything stick
It gives a nice coating on
When it's Friday take that crusty stuff on the outs
Look at it
Play crying for
Look for
What about minutes
What your internal temp on your chicken
About 164 breaths 16525
Dark grey
Chicken
Play store
Complete white check on the inside
Super juicy
And we have
Yeah this is the wrong way to make
Chicken tenders I just want to show you two approaches were reading with that flower we got an egg wash bread
The flower is like the glue and in the end it's going to stick
Breadcrumbs on to the surface on the outside
Three 15 in a joke is we're going to season chicken directly
Next step is really key and a lot of people forget to do this
Seasoned the stages of the
Ok chicken tender when I drop it into the flour and then shake off the excess
Play drop it into the egg mixture to probably want to wear some gloves or at least make sure that you are
Being sanitary about making sure that you're not cross contaminated
Add this right into the flour and one good tricks to keep one hand dryer in one hand
So I'm going to be able to read and when I drop it into dry again when I get this out of I'm using my dry hair
Reduce the second option that we have to do is called reading in this is more the traditional southern Style
Tipping into a little bit of butter milk pictures of tiny little bit at the bottom of the flower
We're going to break it up into pieces this up
I see you got little clubs on there and that was going to create the store
Text reduction queries that we get on the outside of a chicken
Layer chicken down into the basket
Before you drop it into the fryer so then you don't Splash
Cooking times 3 5-minutes should be fine you're always listening for that that is not going in
Chicken into a pan of oil that's too cold
What's going to happen if the chicken is going to absorb the oil like a
Looking for is 165 degrees C in Fahrenheit temperature that's the same temperature
For chicken and I've got it on your 166 right there we'll get
I said we have the chicken this is the 3 stage vetting procedure then we also have the Dragon method
Turn the left today
I'm going to go home in open up my deep fryer now