The movie
This is what about
I knew it would come to this
What you need is a nice big piece of seaweed
Outside so this is the awesome rolling matting
Stephen tries
I am putting rice
Phone David
I usually get a price on the outside
How much rice am I supposed to use enough
I'm putting on the top because it's going to have to roll
Next ingredients go into this machine
This Green
The Ritz
Ok don't worry because when I go to that
Enrol
No it's a rolling
Over this and that over there
This is too big
Unique way to do it
Meatpacking work
Don't message me this way
The something went wrong here
Oh no
Yeah you just dig in there
Call Laurie
Siri
Side of the rough side
Close down
Make sure it's not too hot
Temperature
Spread
Of rice over
Ingredients
Use the roly-poly that's going around it
Pulling the basket
Sushi time we're going to make some maki rolls which is basically the sort of standard roll sushi
This guy right here the perfect for the task
They all look about the same to find out the strings around one way and a baby runs the other and the key here is to make sure
Read directions
To the flat side up and the strings running away from you like this ok
Play slightly smoother shiny side on the lorry and then we have a slightly Corsa side here
If you want to put a smooth side
Against the match in a season
Alright a little bit and we're going to add a pinch of sugar
Dash of rice vinegar
The general rule that the rest of the body
You can't reason it is going to stick to
A really easy trick to avoid that from happening
Tips of your fingers wet while working with the
I'm going to the cinema in a rule of thumb is that your race should be to rain stop
If you were to build a house out of race
Play bricks you want one brick two
That's about it
The only place I wanna leave a gap is
Turn on the top Edge bar furthest away from me
I remember less is more so don't go Overboard
Bursting at the seams
Runaway couple steps
In here
What does around one third of the way up
I do is roll this inward and then
It's like a wave breaking in the ocean
I want to pull me
Map towards me as well
Ok so when I come down
Towards me
As I make my
Is it going to rain tonight
Vegetable maki roll