Cooker shows always against one person with an accent
Peel and cube
Ok so we need a pillow over here
Weather
Note that
This isn't working
How far something out really well
I cut myself
Add a slight incident so cubing the potato
What's the name you just like butter
Replace the cube
You want YouTube stuff like the round
Picasso would be proud of course
Tube in Peel this I'm gonna use this potato peeler to peel away
So I don't cut myself
Hold your fingers make her like you
Knuckleball
I remember doing this myself
Like surgery
And took you soon as possible
Get yourself a flat surface
Download like this
I don't like the turning in movie
My name is perfect
You want to get things as closest to a consistent size which sadly to say this is not
When is perfect cube potatoes Romania net worth
Does your playlist
Sewing appeal in Cuba potato here to fill this potato
This is pretty straightforward
What we looking to do is make perfect and even
Tubes out of the potato
In order to get perfect cubes or we can have to do is have some fun
Please guys can become mashed potatoes
Any number of operations the first thing I want to do is even up the shape
Get rid of birds from here
To come across and we're going to cut this into
Planks planks into rectangles
I'm going to come back across the other direction and we're going to cut these
One more
This is a bunch of matching
All done I think they're close enough
It's potatoes