Now
How do I get a new clothes
A poached egg
The dirty eggs
Sunny Side Up over easy
It looks something like this
I have no clue
You guys are not fair this is pressure
Nice and easy
Very close to a poached egg
Is it
I think this
Was a little bit crap
Wickes
I think they're the egg is becoming gradually more delicious as tango
A cooks itself
In the water
Not directly in the water
Amelia Monet
Work
Tarot reading work
A bit like egg drop soup
Yeah I'm just gonna hold this year
Keep it swelling together somehow
Maybe I need to
All the whites place
Ok
Well
Willie haughey
Konosuba
In boiling water
Boiling water
Small amounts of vinegar
American football
You spin the water bit making a world
Because this way consolidates the egg white
It's going in a different Direction
Set alarm from a guy name
Emeril lagasse
Ok we're texting and then you clap it in the service of the water and drop it
Centre of the Earth
Winter dinner doesn't leave it
I like my poached eggs over a bit runny so as soon as they are
Little loose
Hard boiled egg
The slab on somebody's playlist is rude
He's dumped me
Ok so we are going to poach an egg
I meant to look inside the pot here and where to find water
For putting an egg
All the way
Any just turn it back on
So when a Jew is reduced by heat
Just a little bit down to a simmer look like
Especially running up the side of the pen without any word bubbles breaking the surface of the water
Keep the temperature relative to spread out in the world
Some other acid that would be fine because what's happening here is the acid is going to calculate what I mean
Is going to go like that
If we got the acid in the water what's going to happen again it's going to spread out everywhere
Water in the park
So I'm just going to hear from you to drop eggs into the water works really well here is actually to create
Like a whirlpool in the park sucked into the centre of that world
Reduce the voting age
Is the keyboard close eye on the temperature and constantly adjust as it cooks and
Put into the water
Some people into a small ball in the war
That's up to you but I would avoid it's cracking the egg on the side of a pot
Go for a flat surface
Just a quick break and we just going to drop that right into the
Shouldn't stick to anything and it shouldn't
Spread out in the party you can see it's already starting to coagulate or colour
Bunch up on itself
Gerald umbrella radio on supermarket large egg cooking in about 3 minutes
So when you find this fish batter was really effectively at removing it
Is the water very well and it's got a nice soup for picking up the egg out of the park when we got into the yolk itself
The perfect degree of doneness mean
Egg white in a nice runny egg