It looks like a scary face a little bit on the side
Do you like see the eyes
Make a horror movie
Oh my
Ask the Peter
Like
In the air
Oh this is a disaster ok
Can I put flower on it
Stereo
What that probably way too much
This isn't going well
Now the fun part
Fahrenheit
Tesco SIM not working
No idea had a task
Ageing 20 years because of the stress
Ok we're going to pass this weekend but you don't use it
What you want to do is just use your fingertips and stop pressing from the middle
Play too hard take your time
I like to do the work
Get it on your knuckles and when it like
Drag down with the weight of its do you just like shut your face
Spinach
TJ Hughes
Do something like that
I feel like a
Look at isn't attractive
We are toss pizza dough
So starting with a good pizza dough so I'm going to actually
Put it directly into his balls
How long left on my boring have a little extra flower on top
First I'm going to put it down
People want to use a rolling pin
Crispbread or flatbread pizza so I have my flat
And what I'm going to do
I'm going to start to press down my
Continually turning it
What's the tips of my fingers what I'm going to do now I'm going to start to stretch
The doll with my hair
Instead of tossing it for the most part I'm going to take it
And start to
Let me do it work to do the work for me
Ok
If you want you can put on the back to you
I'm going to sleep
When you stretch a day like this one is your knuckles not your things you think so
Play some you're just passing it to move around on your knob
So now I got to have a nice cross it's fairly saying I can start to cook
You can just turn on your pain now
Shut up