Is it a trick
I think I can do that
Does cracking on the side
Separate the yolk
How is broken
Listen to garbage
Kobe
What's that yoke
It's weird
Wow this is so f******
Is pretty easy
Crackerjack play
I'm gonna trade back and forth here
I putting the baby inside the shell
This is doing it for me
Right
I actually don't think
So the first thing when you're cracking an egg you should be doing it
What service is opposed to a sharp surface because that's going to keep you from getting the shell
And I always separate between my fingers
This is primarily because the show has sharp edges so my fingers are less likely to Wake Me Up
What that is