Oh nah
You want me to cry
I don't really like onions on my sounds
I should like goggles
Yeah I'm not really good with onions
I have no clue this is the right way
Icw on Rachael Ray show
I want to daytime television
Deers are just reaching my eye
People put themselves through the device frozen
I had to do it again I would
Find a better way of doing
Turn off the tap
Can you cut it in half
Make a little slit in the middle here
Get rid of the skin breakdown
And then it's on the way
Most people in this way but really want to do is collect from root to stem
Onion in half first thing
Leaving the root end and tax I'm going to take a little bit of a stem that's going to loosen up the skin for me
Feel the skin back
So you want to be using the service that you can find because when you use it
Individual cells and that means we're going to release more of those juices that are really going to irritate your eyes
Ring temperature will be more likely to make you cry in the fridge an hour before you take my shifts
Turn that sideways parallel with my cutting board and come across and one horizontal
Maybe 3 depending on the size of your onions almost all the way through but not white
How to turn my onions with the room facing away from me
X12
5 when I come back
Pretty much data itself when I get to the root beer then I can just get rid of that guy
Play Simon's group