What I'm gonna do is try to do Mickey Mouse ears
Because I like to have fun
Pear cake
Oh my god
Well I never
I'll do my best
Canola oil on 2%
Work it out
Everyone that I forgot
That looks better
Is this like a professional cake making thing this is this
We are pouring the batter in the my god
You're not round and pretty but hopefully going to taste good
Antique is knowing when it's right up there
You just want to help it
I think it's time
It's
Oliver smoke
I'm sorry
I will be honest and never make my own
Oh my God make some for me
Which is the worst thing to say I am 30 years old
Ok I've made pancakes many many times
Amy from this morning actually of canola and butter
Do you want to just put in a continuous stream right from the middle so you just
Do you like that you don't move
Your later
Sonam is waiting for like a little bubbles to come later
There you go with starting to get bubbles
Can you check the underside to see
Nice colour in the news in a simply
Flip it right over
And then I go like to fight in it
That's pretty much it's probably close to down at this point
Here we go a delicious on a circular tank
You know it's 2018 pancakes can be whatever they want
This is the way you make me
People make
They're on their way but this is my way I make pancakes
First we start with a pan of butter I use whole butter
Four flavour
Just agree Savannah
Swirl around
You don't want so much it is but it's brand new just wanted to be bubbling away ok I'm going to get my bed
Unusual anal
Or large stone
Why pick the better up I give it back in so I can get a lot of trips
And then I'm going to add to my pan right
Slowly put in the pen and then swirl
Lightly so I get that nice round pancake
I like to use a riddle if you have a grill at home
Will give you a more space to work in
What I'm looking for is this if you look right here
Does little bubbles have starter pack
What's the bubbles of top star to appear
Dennis ready the flip if you flip it before that
It's going to splatter everywhere you need to get pancakes to look more like a rush act Esther off
Pink blood testing you are going to have her around
I'm using a firm spatula and now you can see that I'm sorry to get some bubbles on the tap I get on to it really quickly
NIA
Ok
Strawberry quick
What I'm waiting for now is just so this other side sets we don't need to cook it how much on the other side and weird
Do I play pancakes super simple
Personally second on top of each other
Right
I like the classic way salted butter or unsalted butter
Nothing better than their contrast between the saltiness of butter
The fluffy pancakes in the sweetness of maple syrup
Real maple syrup as a better flavour than a commercial pancake syrup
Anatomy
Koala
Enable serial
Reminder for 8