Don't
Your eyes
Dyson
David Turner seeds
I'm going to get it on my fingers
I think I can do this
Not sure what I should do here
The Scissor everywhere
I'm going to cut I did see a tool that I could use to big
Standard issue
There's still some season here that's alright
Just enough so you don't choke one of my specialties
A more elegant way
How to deseed a pepper
Who's the first cut off the stem
Cut your paper in half
So that you can open it right up this fibre and out
Play some mirror
Cutting into strips
And then take those strips and cut down
I just need it so see you not going down
How's the baddest
So we're going to deseed a jalapeno and I find the easiest way is the actually
Take one side off of the jalapeno
And take the next side
One more time
That was behind the scenes with her heart you always have better
Stop with your cutting if you leave the skin side of the healthy
Facing the board as opposed to facing up
The first thing I'm going to do is take these ribs out which is the lighter colour pack
Come in with my knife sideways
And just slide right through
What are the ribs removed
My First Cut is When We Collide Julianne which is the longest river
By Juliana
Come back across
Daiso juliennes into cubes
I felt like a culinary phone
Music
Gangster music
Fresh produce