Just go for it
Romanian martini
Is it going to be interesting
So I don't know what's in a martini you gave me everything so can I use everything usually have to shake something
So I'm just not exactly sure how much I'm sorry
It's like two parts something one part something
I have no idea
I'm just bought some stuff in here and see what happens
2 oz burger
One-and-a-half parts of chin
This is not really going to 19s school
LEGO little remove
Play maybe
Shake it
Now that we have our souls to decorate the glass we're just going to go for the Poor
Get this off anymore
Gardener
Do you drink a dice yes you do
Put some liquor mixed together
Oh my god
What else goes in your martini
Remind me 2 minutes before 2 and quarter hours gym
2 half hours DragonVale
I think gin tastes disgusting so I'm gonna make a vodka martini
Remove between a quarter and a half ounce
Let's make it a dirty Martini
Nice
Turner James Bond now
Can you pour down
Couple of olives in there at 3
World of Mana
Let's go direct
How to make a martini
I get some ice before I even start to make my drink I'm going to chill my glass
Ice in my glass
Anna Willoughby no water
Dale City nice and chill
The classic debate with a martini is shaken or stirred if you shake it is going to be watered down
If you start this going to be a little stronger in super
With good quality vodka you do better for our support for this ok
Ok so I measure it out
When I get my lights
Don't be scared beyond the ice nice and tight
Lois I have my finger
On the top and I'm driving my hand around the Shakers and it doesn't fly off good salad shape
Yes we want to see
Frost
Or condensation on the top of shower and after dinner speaker
So what I'm going to do now is going to take my class
I'm going to jump out my ice water give it a shake it in the excess water out
How long am I from live forever my remove interlock is basically this out
The basically I'm just going to swirl around
Just so I get the taste of removed in early April
Shake It Up
How many M3 for Alves
Collar for small ones
Nice and cold
Porto V aves
Make sure you get it all out
I'm looking for those nice chips at the top
And that's how you make a vodka martini
Hello
Just to be sure