I have never even heard of an over easy egg
Really creative
Over easy egg I don't know what that means
Let's see what happens
I'm going to butter this
Everything
What's happened
Extra calcium
I feel like over easy eggs is supposed to be burnt and disgusting
Dimplex
What they have done
Scoop of that
Oh you know what I was thinking of his Sunny Side Up does that mean oh no
Rxl
Oh my god
Entirely sure
What constitutes an over easy egg
How do I ever actually go to a restaurant
Fancy eggs
Ok I won't make another easier over easy means that we
Gently
Turn it over
The other side
First step is a little little tiny baby oil
I'm going to break your hand
Will Alsop
Pepper on top
Wait for it to set around the metal checking around the edges to see that it's gonna Lift up nicely
And then I'm going to put it over
Just go for it Flip It Over
Flip in the air
Learning about 10 seconds still be done
Over easy egg
First drive
Another easy egg is an egg that the white is set on both sides
TripAdvisor
And the yoke is still
So I get my pen
Warm not super hot I'm getting a little bit of
Oil is best for over easy eggs because they keep the Browning down if you use butter the butter sauce the brown before the egg is cooked in
Can you get brown crispy
Get to where the oil is just trying to catch a shimmer
And run around the pan and then break your right into the pain
I really don't want much movement when I go to the pier
You can see that it's starting to just like Lisa
At this point we need to add all of this on
I always season 8 have my eggs
20 assault
Nothing worse than a brand
I know you can see this trying to say
There's two
Parts to the white the white on the outside surface that is an inside part of the white
Can I watch a start ASAP before I flip it if I flip over for them
The engine the car falls apart
That's when you start to break BO2 things start to get messy
So you can see them outside
History of the
Get undressed really aggressive
What's the way to set on the other side and I don't want to cook in anymore
Ok so I'm going to take it off the heat
Am I going to play
You want to get a special cos he just said that to the you give me an oil that actually in the pen on
Play that's what you know what you want a greasy
Ovaries
I really rate test to see if your egg is right is the
You can see that my joke is running
Demo white is fully
Get me some toast this is for you
Anatomy
Haha